{
    "subject": "resource/Museo_del_Traje",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Spain",
    "human_readable": "Museo del Traje is located in Spain.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9382702708244324,
            "question": "Where is the Museo del Traje located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9286482930183411,
            "question": "What is the significance of the Museo del Traje in Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.789589524269104,
            "question": "Can visitors learn about Spanish fashion history at the Museo del Traje?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7328494787216187,
            "question": "What type of museum is the Museo del Traje?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6303938627243042,
            "question": "What kind of artifacts are likely housed in the Museo del Traje?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6140288710594177,
            "question": "What country is home to the Museo del Traje?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5801512598991394,
            "question": "Is the Museo del Traje a popular tourist destination?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4396408796310425,
            "question": "Are there any special events or exhibitions hosted at the Museo del Traje?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3448840081691742,
            "question": "Would you expect to find contemporary fashion exhibits at the Museo del Traje?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26666104793548584,
            "question": "Does the Museo del Traje focus on a specific historical period?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Museo del Traje is located in Spain.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7055_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Would you expect to find contemporary fashion exhibits at the Museo del Traje?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7055_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any special events or exhibitions hosted at the Museo del Traje?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7055_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the Museo del Traje a popular tourist destination?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7055_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7055_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7055_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7055_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7055_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7055_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7055_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7055_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7055_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7055_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7055_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents repeatedly mention that the Museo del Traje is located in Madrid, Spain."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the Museo del Traje is located in Madrid, which is a city in Spain. Therefore, the statement \"Museo del Traje is located in Spain\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}